# Krishna Adhikari

#### Student

- Lahachowk Machhapuchchhre-4, Gandaki, 33700
- adhikarikrishna1.com.np

986 654 4323

twitter.com/forkhakitech

forkhakitech@gmail.com

Respectful self-motivator gifted at finding reliable solutions for software issues. Experienced in Mobile freelancing and Programming and offering skills in Designing and Development. Fluent in English, Hindi and Nepali and accustomed to working with cross-cultural, global teams.



### Skills

- Programming
- Public Speaking
- Designing
- Singing
- Hacking
- Application Development



000

- Good 0000
- Good 0000 Good
- 000 Good
- Very Good



### Work History

IT Technical Support

International Youth Society, Kathmandu, Province 3

IT Consultant Agritech Nepal, Pokhara, Gandaki

# 2019-04 - Current

2019-05 - 2019-08

## Education

2015-04 - 2017-03

Amarsingh Model Secondary School - Ramghat-12, Pokhara

2017-05 - 2019-06 NEB: (Science)

KEF Secondary School - Simpani-1, Bagar

2019-08 - Current

Bachelor of Computing Informatics College Pokhara - Matepani, Pokhara

# Software

Guide To Termux Tools

